{
    "question": "Mohon berikan contoh soal mengenai persuading",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Persuading adalah mempengaruhi lawan bicara untuk melakukan atau mengerjakan sesuatu seperti yang diharapkan pihak pertama<br><br>COntoh\u00a0<br>Mengajak bermain basket<br>Hi my brother, would you be so kind to accompany me playing basketball? I will give you a chocolate if you would like to play it with me.\u00a0",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "when do you go to school about 10 minutes later?",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "1-see-his-to-if-go-doesnt-at-house-aldi-will-her-school-see-co-389",
            "question": "1.\u00a0see-his-to-if-go-doesn't-at-house-aldi-will-her-school-see-cousin-he-her-to    2. and-holiday-bali-if-have-will-his-lombok-long-go-year-Mr.Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\r\nkalo disusun jadi conditional sentence ini jadinya apa ya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "no.2 Mr kukuh and his family will go to bali and lombok if they have a long holiday this year",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-contoh-pecakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pemesanan-meja-di-618",
            "question": "Buatlah contoh pecakapan bahasa inggris tentang pemesanan meja di restoran..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i want to ask permission<br>B: yes of course<br>A: two days there will be an event in my home, can i order 2 pieces of table<br>B: of course may be happy<br>A: ok i&#039;ll wait for tomorrow<br>B: okay, thank you&#039;ve booked a table here<br>A: you&#039;re welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>A: Good afternoon <br>b: Good afternoon, can I help you? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table, for tomorrow afternoon? <br>b: yes, it could. for how many people? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table for lunch two people! <br>B: Yes sir, tomorrow daytime table number five <br>A: Thank you<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aku-belum-mengerti-dengan-jelas-tentang-past-perfect-tense-523",
            "question": "Aku belum mengerti dengan jelas tentang past perfect tense.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The PAST PERFECT TENSE indicates that an action was completed (finished or \"perfected\") at some point in the past before something else happened. This tense is formed with the past tense form of \"to have\" (HAD) plus the past participle of the verb (which can be either regular or irregular in form):\n    I had walked two miles by lunchtime. \n    I had run three other marathons before entering the Boston Marathon .",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>ita menggunakan Past Perfect (simple) tense untuk menunjukkan suatu tindakan di masa lalu berkaitan dengan tindakan lain sebelumnya di masa lalu. Bisa juga\u00a0pengertian Past perfect tensedigunakan utuk menjelaskan kalau sesuatu terjadi saat sebelum waktu spesifik.</span>Penggunaan Past Perfect Tense1. menceritakan sebuah tindakan yang sudah selesai sebelum tindakan lain di masa laluRumus = had + past participleContoh:<span>a.You had studied math before you moved to los angeles.<br>Kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>b. You had not studied math before you moved to Los angeles.<br>Kamu belum belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>c. Had you studied math before you moved to los angeles?<br>Apakah kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum ke los angeles?<br>2. kalimat pengandaian (Conditional Sentence) Type III</span><span>If + subject + Past perfect + would have + verb III<br>If we had known the answer, we would have told you<br>Seandainya kami telah tahu jawabannya, kami akan telah mengatakan padamu (kenyataanya kami sudah tidak tahu jawabannya)</span><span>3. kalimat tak langsung (reported speech)<br>Reported speech adalah kalimat yang digunakan untuk menjelaskan perkataan seseorang. Kalimat ini mengubah dialog menjadi kalimat biasa<br>Ann: I have searched all the rooms.<br>George: Ann said she had searched all the rooms.<br>George : Ann mengatakan bahwa dia sudah mencari semua kamar</span>untuk pembahasan selengkapnya tentang reported speech dalam berbagai tenses disini3 Rumus Past Perfect Tense<span>\u2022 Positif (+)<br>Subject + had + verb III + (past participle) + object<br>\u2022 Negatif (-)<br>Subject + had + not + verb III + object<br>\u2022 Tanya (?)<br>Had + subject + verb III + object ?</span>Contoh kalimat \u2013 Past Perfect tense:<span>They had been here before 1945 (+)<br>- mereka telah berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>They had not been here before 1945 (-)<br>- mereka belum berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>Had they been here before 1945 ? (?)<br>- apakah mereka telah berada disini sebelum 1945 ?</span><span>She had gone to Amsterdam when I called her (+)<br>- dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>She had not gone to Amsterdam when I called her (-)<br>- dia belum pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>Had she gone to Amsterdam when you called her ?<br>- apakah dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika kamu meneleponnya ?</span><span>Keterangan waktu (Adverb of time) yang umum digunakan dalam\u00a0past Perfect tense:<br>after, before, already, as soon as, just, yet, until, till, by the time that.</span><span>Past Perfect tense\u00a0juga digunakan untuk ungkapan seperti : \u201cI wish\u201d, \u201cas if/though\u201d and \u201cif only\u201d.</span><span>\u2022 I wish I hadn\u2019t gone there ( aku berharap aku tidak pernah pergi kesana )<br>\u2022 Jono looked as if he had done something terrible. ( Jono tampak seolah-olah ia telah melakukan sesuatu yang mengerikan )</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bahasa-inggris-nya-dikejar-190",
            "question": "Bahasa inggris nya dikejar?? ...",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<strong><em>be pursued<br><br>jadiin yang terbaik yah kakak</em></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "klu nggasalah <br><span>chased</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jelasin-tentang-present-perfect-tense-920",
            "question": "Jelasin tentang present perfect tense\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present perfect adalah tenses yang menyatakan bahwa kejadian sudah dilakukan.<br>Rumus : S + Have/Has(Auxiliary) + V3<br>Misal : I have done my homework<br>Unsur : I = Subject<br>Have = Aux/Have/Has<br>Done = V3<br>Homework = Object<br>Umumnya ditambahkan kata Since + Time<br>Jadi : I have done my homework since this morning<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "present perfect itu berhubungan dengan kejadian yang sudah selesai. kata kuncinya sih ada kata \"sudah\", \"baru saja\", dsb.<br><br>misalkan \"saya sudah mengerjakan PR\", atau i have done my homework<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantu-nyusun-kata-kata-ne-jadi-klimat-yg-bner-ya-yang-dimulai-dri-452",
            "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "narrative-text-yang-bagus-dan-jarang-di-dengar-orang-797",
            "question": "Narrative text yang bagus dan jarang di dengar orang??",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The story snow white<br>In earlier times there lived a , who named Snow White . He lived with his aunt and uncle because his parents died . One day she heard her uncle and aunt talking about leaving Snow White in the castle because they wanted to go to America and they did not have enough money to take Snow White with them . princess Snow White did not want her uncle and aunt to do this . So he decided to escape .<br><br><span>\u00a0The next day he ran away from home when her aunt and uncle were having breakfast , he fled into the wood . In the wood she felt very tired and hungry . Then she saw this cottage . She knocked but no one answered her so she went inside and felt asleep Meanwhile seven dwarfs came home from his work . They get into . There, they found Snow White woke up from his sleep . He saw the dwarfs . The dwarf said : \" What is your name ? &#039; Snow White said , \" My name is Snow White . \" One dwarf said , \" If you want , you can stay here with us . &#039; Snow White tells all about her story . Then daughter snow and the seven dwarves are now living happily ever after .</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}